cogispan.com 2014-12-22

# Privacy & Terms of Use | Cogispan Car Reviews

AutoReviewsOnline only collects the information that we need in order to deliver services and information to you. We do not use techniques to collect personal information about you without your knowledge. 

We do not use or disclose your personal information for any purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with your consent or as required by law. 

RETENTION: Your personal information is retained only as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes. Cogispan Car Reviews Inc. does not keep your personal information if it is no longer needed for the purposes required or as required by law. 

Upon request in writing, you will be informed of the existence, use, and disclosure of your personal information and you will be given access to that information. We will assist any customer who informs us that they need assistance in preparing a request concerning personal information. You may challenge the accuracy and completeness of the information and have it amended as appropriate. 

ACCESSING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION FILE: If you wish to review or verify the personal information in your file or find out to whom we have disclosed it, you can do so by writing to us at the following address: 

Cogispan Car Reviews Privacy Officer  
4261-A14 Hwy 7 East, Suite 884  
Unionville, Ontario L3R 9W6  
or e-mail us at editor@cogispan.com

Cogispan Car Reviews Inc. has thirty (30) days to reply to a request for access to a file. Cogispan Car Reviews Inc. can refuse access to a file in certain circumstances. 

ACCURACY OF YOUR FILE: You can ask to delete or correct any information contained in your file. The request for correction must be made by writing to us, either by mail at the above-mentioned mailing address, or by e-mail at the above-mentioned e-mail address. Cogispan Car Reviews Inc. has thirty (30) days to reply.

When you visit www.cogispan.com without registering or otherwise interacting with the site, your personal information and e-mail address are not recorded. Cogispan Car Reviews Inc. provides a number of services via www.cogispan.com. To access these services, we may require you to identify yourself or provide personal information. We use the information you have provided to help us serve you better. We will require personal information when you make purchases, take part in surveys, or request information on the products and services offered by Cogispan Car Reviews Inc. 

We do not send unsolicited e-mail. If you add your name to an e-mail subscriber’s list on our Website, you authorize Cogispan Car Reviews Inc. to send to you personalized messages from time to time. These messages contain information about services offered by Cogispan Car Reviews Inc. and its partners that we think may be of interest to you. At no time do cogispan.com’’s advertisers, partners, or third parties have access to your confidential information. You may cancel your subscription to these e-mail messages at any time. 

AutoReviewsOnline uses standard Web server log files to help us count visitors and evaluate our site’s technical capacity. We use this information to find out how many people visit our web site and to make our pages more useful to our visitors. 

When you leave our web site: This policy discloses the privacy practices for our Web site. However, our site contains links to other sites. Once you link to another site, you are subject to the privacy and security policies of the new site. We encourage you to read the Privacy Policies of all Web sites you visit, especially if you share any personal information.

Electronic Communications

AutoReviewsOnline cannot guarantee the confidentiality of any information transmitted over the Internet, accordingly, email transmissions should not contain confidential information and AutoReviewsOnline will not be liable for errors, omissions or alterations made or caused by email communications.

Copyright & Terms of Use

AutoReviewsOnline owns and reserves copyright in this web site. Users are free to download information for personal use. None of the information or imagery on this web site may be reproduced, distributed or published for any other purpose without the prior consent of AutoReviewsOnline.

All contents of the AutoReviewsOnline Web Site are Copyright © 2011 AutoReviewsOnline and/or its sponsors, contributors or suppliers. All rights reserved.
